{
    "subject": "resource/Angel_Planells",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "Spanish artist",
    "human_readable": "Angel Planells is a Spanish artist.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8640336394309998,
            "question": "Is Angel Planells a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7722655534744263,
            "question": "Is Angel Planells known for a particular style of art?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7024070024490356,
            "question": "Where has Angel Planells exhibited his art?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6059074401855469,
            "question": "What nationality is Angel Planells?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5832935571670532,
            "question": "What kind of art does Angel Planells create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4792576730251312,
            "question": "Does Angel Planells work in the arts?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46482348442077637,
            "question": "Where is Angel Planells from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45680221915245056,
            "question": "What profession does Angel Planells have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24012865126132965,
            "question": "What inspires Angel Planells's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11960512399673462,
            "question": "Has Angel Planells received any awards for his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Angel Planells is a Spanish artist.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1598_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What inspires Angel Planells's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1598_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What profession does Angel Planells have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1598_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Angel Planells from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1598_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1598_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1598_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1598_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1598_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1598_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1598_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1598_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1598_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1598_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1598_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Angel Planells is a Spanish artist.\" Multiple sources indicate that he was born in Cadaqu\u00e9s, Spain, and was involved in painting and surrealism, confirming his status as a Spanish artist."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}